sellersourcebook.com 2007-12-11

# The Seller Sourcebook : Privacy Policy

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used at The Seller Sourcebook. We take extraordinary steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. 

**_Information Collection_**   
The Seller Sourcebook is the sole owner of the information collected from our website. We do not, or will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in our privacy statement below. 

**_Cookies_**   
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the visitor's hard drive containing information about the visitor. Advertisers connected to The Seller Sourcebook at times require cookies to track statistics about products and locations, but at no time are these linked to any personal identification. At this time, The Seller Sourcebook uses cookies only for login convenience. 

**_Log Files_**   
The Seller Sourcebook keeps log files on broad fields to analyze trends, track user movements, and gather data for demographic locations. This is not attached in anyway to visitor's personal identification. 

**_Sharing_**   
At this time, The Seller Sourcebook does not share any information with advertisers, merchants, or any other third party. 

**_Links_**   
Links to other sites outside of The Seller Sourcebook do not apply to this privacy statement. We are not responsible for privacy policies of other websites linked to The Seller Sourcebook. Please read the privacy statement of each website linked to The Seller Sourcebookfor information and data use for visitor's personal identification. Our privacy statement applies solely to The Seller Sourcebook. 

**_Contests_**   
At any particular time, The Seller Sourcebook may conduct contests for our visitor's. Visitor participation for these contests is voluntary, and in no way requires the visitor to give out personal information when choosing not to enter in the contest. Collected information may include contact information and demographic information, such as name, e-mail, address, state, ect. This information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. 

**_Newsletter_**   
After registering for a Subscription, you are automatically subscribed to our Newsletter. You can either elect to subscribe or unsubscribe at any time. All information stored on our database is not shared or sold to any third party what so ever. 

**_Sending to a Friend_**   
When a visitor chooses to send News, Articles, Reviews, ect, to a friend, the names and e-mail addresses are not logged. The Seller Sourcebook will send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit our site. The Seller Sourcebook will never send another e-mail to the visitor or friend for any purpose. 

**_Changes of our Policy_**   
If and when our policy statement changes, visitors with Memberships in our databases will be notified of the changes, and provided a link to this page to view the changes. If a visitor decides that our policy does not benefit them, they can use the opt-out option at anytime.
